

PROFILE

I am an organised, efficient and hard-working person having 3 years' experience on IT development, am willing to discover and accept new ideas which can be put into practice effectively. I am a good listener and learner, able to communicate well with a group and on an individual level. I can motivate and direct my talents and skills to meet objectives.

TECHNICAL SKILL

ReactJS, Python, Javascript, MySQL, MongoDB, HTML, CSS

Devops:

AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, GitHub, Jenkins, Ansible, Terraform

EDUCATION

NARULA INSTITITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

B tech on Computer Science & Engg. 2017-2021

TAKI HOUSE (BOYS)

Higher Secondary (10+2) 2015-2017

TAKI HOUSE (BOYS)

Madhyamik 2014-2015

ADIRON GUNIN



89, Raja Rajendra Lal Mitra Road, Kolkata, West Bengal



8777 468 432



adirongunin1234@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE (3 YEARS)

HCL TECHNOLOGIES LIMITED

30.09.2022 - Present

- 1) Working as Analyst in Automation Development.
- 2) Worked on project in ReactJS to develop and design the UI based on Client request.
- 3) Python scripting has introducted with Flask framework to process server side operation.
- 4) Have used different Hooks like useState,useEffect,useRef etc in ReactJS to process data in real time.
- 5) MongoDB performs a major role to store all the logs, user details, Backup to retrive data in future.
- 6) Devops mechanism has been used for creating CI/CD pipeline using Git, Docker and Jenkins.
- 7) Designed AWS instances for deployment the build into test servers for QA.
- 8) Used Ansible to connect servers to configure.

WEBSKITTERS TECHNOLOGY SOLUTION PVT LTD

01.05.2021 - 27.09.2022

- 1) Worked as Software developer.
- 2) Handle Multiple projects with differnet technologies like PHP, ReactJS, Python and WordPress.
- 3) Experience direct client interaction for feedback collection and modification.
- 4) Have done RnD on different projects to implement new technology.
- 5) Experienced on Git interaction to perfrom version control mechanism.

CERTIFICATION

Certification on Cloud Computing and DevOps